

BEHRAM BEN ÇELEN

ABOUT ME

Hello I am Behram, I have been working in this industry professionally for 10+ years. I took an active role many projects. I took place as a speaker at many software conferences. Also in love with Open source.

I take great pleasure in developing high quality applications and sharing my knowledge and experience with people.

PROFILE

https://behram.dev https://github.com/behram https://www.linkedin.com/in/behramcelen https://www.udemy.com/user/behramcelen http://www.slideshare.net/behramcelen

behramcelen@gmail.com +48 796 813 589

Wroclaw/Poland

EXPERIENCE

PHP Developer

Deepkod Freelance Group, Ankara (Turkey) 2012-2014

Backend Developer (PHP)

Bulut Yazilim A.Ş,Istanbul (Turkey) 2014-2018

Full-stack Developer (DevOps/PHP/React)

Youthall, Istanbul (Turkey) https://www.youthall.com 2018-2020

Backend Developer (PHP/Symfony)

Expertshare, Baden (Switzerland) https://expertshare.live/2020-2022

Full-stack Developer (PHP/Symfony/React)

Denkplan, Baden (Switzerland) https://denkplan.com/?lang=en 2020-2022

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

Wrocław University of Science and Technology (Poland) 2017 - 2021

TECHNOLOGIES

- PHP*
- Symfony*
- Laravel
- Elasticsearch
- *SQL
- Git
- AWS
- Docker
- JavaScript
- Tornado
- Linux
- Node.js

- Redis
- Pub/Sub
- RabbitMQ
- Freqtrade
- Yii Framework
- Mercure
- API Development
- socket.io
- Python
- WebRTC
- Google Cloud
- ..